Basically, you have to give a customer a survey, give them a gift card, and you have to send them money for free.
And if you think you are doing a good job, I will speak personally.
But if I think this guy is making some sense, I will tell him to come to my program and give me regular feedback.
We will hire that guy to give us feedback.
I did the same with Cursair. They are the first employees, the first users of Cursair.
They are the first ones to launch. They talk to their users in Discord.
They say, I want this feature, I want that feature.
And those good people say, come, you make it.
All their employees were their first users.
This is what we are going to do.
I am going to give them a very heavy feedback cycle.
We will ensure that we don't let every customer satisfy.
We are not going to do it funnily.
The happy path.
The one who is satisfied with everything, the one who is dissatisfied with the other failures, we don't care about them.
No, we don't care about each other.
So you don't worry, bro.
We are not going to leave them at this point.
We are not going to let them bring new customers.
In general, if I come across a website and I feel that the website has put in a lot of effort.
And the person says that we are working in a monster's basement.
I will have no problem with that.
I will appreciate the honesty.
In new age, bro.
This is a too long discussion.
No, trust is a must.
Okay, you want to appear polished.
Because maybe that is important for investment.
I don't trust anyone.
If you think that this website has been launched and there is traffic on the website.
Okay.
Then we have to see if two or three of them will come.
100 people have seen it.
On the home-loan channel.
Okay.
And if 100 people have seen it, we have to see if two or three of them will come.
That's it.
First three have come.
Success.
If three have come, then the next three will come.
And if three have come, then three more will come.
And if three have come, then six of them will come.
And if six have come, then nine of them will come.
And if nine of them come, then nine of them will come.
We have to go slowly.
Okay, let's take a picture.
We will...
We will clap.
Every new thing is a new release for me.
I mean...
What is the timeline?
This is a new feature.
Every release is something new.
Okay.
And before that, we have to make a guide.
We have to put tools.
Like...
There are updates in the apps.
I have to get them ready.
I have to get everything ready-made.
We have to go ahead.
I have to get a lot of stuff.
And I have to do it like this.
Not like this.
I mean, you have to see it.
I don't know.
Okay.
We have to go ahead.
Hmm.
So, Sibyl...
Okay, back to Sibyl.
Do we have to keep it like this?
Or do we have to keep it the way we did in the drop-down?
So that it doesn't go in the same range?
No, no.
It's like this.
So that it doesn't go in the same range?
Yes.
Then...
I mean...
The first time I tried...
Yes.
What should I do?
So...
You have to fill in the HIF values.
All the average values.
And you have to fill in the average intelligence in the first shot.
From the beginning.
So this page has landed, right?
Okay.
He needs to know the automatic.
That it should look like this.
If it looks like this, then do it like this.
Hey, wait. I'll put it in later.
Yes. Perfect.
Perfect.
So when it lands, it looks like this.
After filling this form...
It looks like this.
The intelligence comes and then the list comes.
And then the intelligent person says...
That they will recommend that your income...
I mean...
If you do this, it will be this much.
And he said, okay.
Does it look like this?
Try it.
Try it for real.
Then...
If this is the case...
Yes.
Then I'll try it for real.
Okay.
No, no.
I'll try it.
I will try to game this thing.
Yes.
I didn't know this intelligence before.
I'll try it for real.
That is the only way you can extract truth out of me.
First go.
In the second chapter...
Now we are thinking...
From making the product.
Customer.
Now you don't have a problem with yourself.
You don't have to think about the customer.
Whatever may be the case...
But the real customer doesn't need it.
That is if the input is missing.
See how the scene is.
I know the input is missing.
But there are a lot of fallacies in it.
Like...
First of all...
Any product...
If the customer's profile is developed...
This is a big problem for startups.
Their first two customers...
They make the features of the customer.
And they think that the customer gave me money.
I should serve it.
And they end up making that the mass market does not want.
They end up relying on those institutional customers.
This is the first problem.
The second problem is...
The first customer we choose...
We should not choose a single bubble.
This is the second problem.
Otherwise we will make our product catered to them.
And do something different in the mass market.
The first problem is...
Basically...
The first customer has given you a lot of money.
So you feel entitled to that customer.
And you end up screwing yourself for that customer.
You are screwed.
And once that customer's contract is over...
Or he has given you revenue...
Then you are screwed.
And this is a very big problem.
I have seen a startup...
I have seen a startup for a single customer.
I have seen this problem in YC as well.
And the second problem is...
We have made it for a single cohort.
A segment of me.
But how did we do the right sampling?
It looks like this.
If there is a bell curve with standard deviations...
These are the 40,000 income people.
And these are the 5 lakh income people.
So what we need is...
We need equal samples from this...
From this...
All standard deviations.
We need people in between.